[{"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Mr. Speaker, how are you?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "How you are?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, I think pretty well.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "How are you faring with the battle so far?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, they said that to John McCain and he went on to win the nomination.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Do you see it like that this time?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Look, don't be so sure it hasn't worked.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "With hindsight, wouldn't it have been better for you not to be negative but to be more aggressive?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "You know, Harry Truman, in his great re-election campaign, when he was so far behind that Gallup quit-taking polls in mid-September, went after Dewey and the crowd would yell out give them hell, Harry.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "And isn't it time now for you to accept that this negativity has pounded you into a position where, much as you would like to keep it positive, isn't it time you got the old Gingrich fist out and gave Romney a good old smack?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Look, we'd be so much healthier to eliminate all of the complicated election bureaucracy.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "-- buddies and friends of politicians doing this?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, let me start with Governor Palin, who I think has been greatly underestimated in the national news media, whose record as governor, as a reformer, was very formidable.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Tell me about these two things, and one, how important the choice of running mate is, and any further thoughts you have about endorsements are right now from key figures in the party?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, it's very helpful to get endorsements.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "I mean is it important to candidates such as yourself to get the endorsement of people like Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "You know, reminds me of Abraham Lincoln who once said he was reminded of the man who has offered a chance to be tarred and feathered and carried out down the rail, and said, he would decline the honor even though he appreciated the way it was offered.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "What is your message directly to Mitt Romney on the eve of this crucial vote tomorrow?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I am great, Piers.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Herman Cain, how are you?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "The big announcement is going to be a national movement.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What is this big announcement, Herman?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "First of all, Piers, I know the truth.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "But given everything that happened to you and to your family and the toll that it clearly took, would you, knowing all that, have entered the race?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Is she happy about that?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "My endorsement is going to come later.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Where is your endorsement?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that would be against the law to push somebody out of an airplane.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Who should be in the injector seat?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Piers, it's not going to work.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Who should go through to the next round and who should be kicked out?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Let me ask you this question: if Mitt Romney wins in Iowa and wins in New Hampshire, is that game over?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I happen to believe that every one of the candidates in the race right now could beat Barack Obama.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "But which has the best chance right now, do you think, of beating him?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "It depends upon who the person is.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Herman, would you serve under whoever the Republican nominee turns out to be in a future cabinet?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "The job I would most like would be secretary of defense, because I happen to believe that national security is one of our biggest threats.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Which job would you most like?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "But you will guarantee one thing, the gold ties will continue, whatever job you get?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Well, I want to be a good host.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Tell me this: why don't you personally endorse any of the candidates?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Well, first and foremost, Rick Santorum followed my advice and just what I've done every that I've been -- I've been elected governor five times.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "What do you make of those two events?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "RANSTAD: Well, I think he made the decision early on, because four years ago he spent a lot of time and a lot of effort and resources here, and came in second.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "What do you make of that politically?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, we're proud of the fact that we have record-high corn prices and the Iowa economy is stronger than the rest of the country because of agriculture.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I don't know the answer to the second question.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "So I thought that you're in the perfect position, really, to assess where the GOP party is right now, who you think will emerge victorious, and what you think of the debate generally?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "I think it is a sad reality of our time.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Or is it just reaffirming to the public that the kind of Washington in-fighting, squabbling, so on is alive and kicking in the GOP?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Yeah, I am, from time to time.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Are you a betting man?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Well, I think these appear to be the front-runners tomorrow.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Right now, would you be putting any money at all on anybody outside of Mitt Romney, Newt Gingrich, possibly Rick Santorum, getting the nomination?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "No, I don't necessarily think so.", "docId": "120102pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Do you think anybody who comes out of the top three in Iowa tomorrow should pull out of the race?", "qSentId": 540}]